madasafish.com 2005-04-03

# Madasafish Internet - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Madasafish is owned by Brightview Group Limited who recognises the importance of your privacy. This policy explains how Brightview Group Limited ("we") collect information about you and your use of this website ("the Website"), how we use this information, who that information is sent to and how you can view and amend the information we hold about you.

When we refer to 'personal information' in this privacy policy we mean information which identifies you as an individual or is capable of doing so.

How do we collect information about you and your use of the website?

We may collect information about you or your use of the Website:

a. when you agree to subscribe to a service/product we provide and give us information including contact details, date of birth, payment methods, bank details, etc;

b. when you communicate with us/our Customer Services and Technical Support departments;

c. when you subscribe to our newsletters, enter competitions or promotions;

d. when you take part in surveys or provide us with feedback.

To make Madasafish work even better for you, we may collect information about your tastes and preferences based on your use of the Website and we use cookies to analyse site traffic. Cookies are pieces of information placed on your computer's hard drive recording your presence on a Website, which in turn allows us to recognise the computer used to access the site and offer you tailored solutions based on your last visit.

If you do not want to receive cookies you can set your browser to reject them or to notify you when a site tries to place a cookie on your computer. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some of the services on our site.

How do we use your personal information?

We may use this information to:

a. provide you with the products or services you requested and collect payment;

b. to inform you about competitions, promotions or offers and if you enter such competitions, to manage that competition or promotion;

c. let you know about any changes to our services or our site;

d. manage our network;

e. prevent and detect criminal activity, fraud and misuse of or damage to our network;

f. for other administrative purposes and credit checking

Whom do we disclose the information to?

From time to time we will compile aggregate statistics about the Website and we may share them with reputable third parties. These statistics will not contain information that would enable any third party to identify you personally.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties, but only to the extent necessary to provide and operate the services/products you requested, or as otherwise provided by this privacy policy.

We will disclose personal information to comply with all applicable laws and lawful requests by the appropriate authorities.

How long do we keep the data?

Unless there is a specific legal requirement to keep the information, we will retain your personal data for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which the data has been collected or for which it is to be further processed.

Transfer of data outside Europe

We do transfer data outside Europe but in accordance with the Data Protection Act.

How can you find out what personal information we hold about you?

If you want to know what personal information we hold about you, please write to our Customer Services department (using the contact details on the Website at Madasafish contact page) and enclose a cheque for the administration fee of £10 made payable to us. Please give us any relevant details to help us find the information you require.

How you can amend your personal information?

You can at any time ask us to amend your personal information if this is incorrect by contacting Customer Services using the details set out on our Website at Madasafish contact page.

How do we protect your personal information?

We will protect your personal data by all appropriate security measures including the use of secure servers and encryption.

Third party sites

Third party sites that you can access from our website are not covered by our privacy policy and we accept no responsibility or liability for use of personal information by operators of these sites.

Changes to our privacy policy

We may make changes to our privacy policy from time to time. Your continuing use of the Website and of our services/products indicate your agreement to the use of your personal information as set out in this privacy policy.
